A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Commonwealth Fund/Harvard University Fellowship in Health Policy, SG 3, Series 9 FA1469
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Commonwealth Fund/Harvard University Fellowship in Health Policy, SG 3, Series 9
1993-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1469
1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter-size document boxes.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of the RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. This series was transferred to RAC in 2002 as accession 2002:066.
Scope and Contents
This series contains program files and planning records of the Commonwealth Fund/Harvard University Fellowship in Health Policy. The majority of the material is grant administration files documenting the planning and implementation of the Fellowship. These records often include: proposals, administration and budget files, grant products, evaluation reports, related correspondence and background material.
- Bettering the Health of Minority Americans - Program on Managed Care and Minority Communities and Minority Health Policy Fellowship Program (95453) - Articles and Background, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bettering the Health of Minority Americans - Program on Managed Care and Minority Communities and Minority Health Policy Fellowship Program (95453) - Administration and Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bettering the Health of Minority Americans - Program on Managed Care and Minority Communities and Minority Health Policy Fellowship Program (95453) - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bettering the Health of Minority Americans - Program on Managed Care and Minority Communities and Minority Health Policy Fellowship Program (95453) - Journalists, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bettering the Health of Minority Americans - Program on Managed Care and Minority Communities and Minority Health Policy Fellowship Program (95453) - Consultant Reviews, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bettering the Health of Minority Americans - Program on Managed Care and Minority Communities and Minority Health Policy Fellowship Program (95453) - Subcontracts, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Harvard Medical School - Developing Minority Physicians in Health Policy: Planning Grant (95420) - Articles and Background, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
- Harvard Medical School - Developing Minority Physicians in Health Policy: Planning Grant (95420) - Administration and Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Harvard Medical School - Developing Minority Physicians in Health Policy: Planning Grant (95420) - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Harvard Medical School - Developing Minority Physicians in Health Policy: Planning Grant (95420) - Grant Products, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - Proposal Development, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - Articles and Background, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - Administration and Budget, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - Fellowship Brochure Material, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - Grant Products - Evaluation Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - Grant Products - Evaluation Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 20-22)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Reede (970940) - 1999-2000 Applications (Box 4, Folder 23-25)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted - Confidential material.